stepaheadgold: Hi
toolegit2quit_: Wow
crisofilaxx: at least!!
th3_maj0r: yoyo
WistfulFella: Ay George, how's it going
crisofilaxx: you lazzy hacker
kemfic: hey george!
Andrewnagyy: yooooo
suurrend3r: omggg!!
thisisweeezy: yoooooooooo bro
Andrewnagyy: what's up man
Andrewnagyy: long time no see
kemfic: nice chair
suurrend3r: brooooooooo
toolegit2quit_: What is chill ?
suurrend3r: why ??
Andrewnagyy: How's Comma.ai
linlam123: yooo ma man
alluxua: Long time no see, geohot
suurrend3r: good to see you back
WistfulFella: Notice us BibleThump
linlam123: gaaraIQ gaaraIQ
littlebighead82: neaceBang neaceBang
roosterhax: Yo
suurrend3r: I stop follow you because I think you'll never be streaming again
suurrend3r: thought*
alluxua: cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1
suurrend3r: PogChamp PogChamp
WistfulFella: Saw Apple became a Trillion worth company? @tomcr00s3
WistfulFella: Okay, sorry : (
roosterhax: learning to use odometry for drone autonomously control
Andrewnagyy: Have you seen the thread about the ex Tesla employee talking about the tech stack hell that's running on the back-end?
quillford: are you ever gonna work on twitch chess again?
linlam123: does he have any emotes???
Andrewnagyy: Am I allowed to post links?
alluxua: What he is coding? SLAM ?
Andrewnagyy: https://twitter.com/atomicthumbs/status/1032939617404645376
kemfic: https://forums.somethingawful.com/showthread.php?threadid=3862643&userid=0&perpage=40&pagenumber=70#post487335699
WistfulFella: The Stock market doesn't interest you, George? @tomcr00s3
roosterhax: yeah he's making it possible so we can have level 5 autonomous driving
WistfulFella: ^
alluxua: I trust Elon musk took Tesla private tweet. Hating myself so much
kemfic: I'm gonna look through that multi-view geometry textbook you'd mentioned, then try to follow along lol
linlam123: only 30 ppl here?
linlam123: gaaraThump
desg92: good
th3_maj0r: lol
WistfulFella: @alluxua I like how he's not too arrogant, he listened to the investors and changed his mind
alluxua: That is a big lie. Elon musk never get funding secured.
kemfic: oh boy my favorite
alluxua: Geohot, how about we hear your new rap : interlude?
th3_maj0r: Did you work offstream on twitchslam?
alluxua: To be honest, geohot sings way better than those singers
suurrend3r: thats a new chair
WistfulFella: How much was it? I hear they're expensive those days
KhaosVFX: why don't you do periscopes anymore George?
WistfulFella: Uber Eats SeemsGood
KhaosVFX: @tomcr00s3
alluxua: He promoted himself to software engineer
KhaosVFX: yikes
kemfic: he's not the social media intern anymore
WistfulFella: I like how you're transparent and honest, I might consider donating
th3_maj0r: Maybe another chair, just 70$ more
linlam123: if i donate 1 dolla ..how r u gonna spend it ? :)
roosterhax: more harware, like multiple screens or parallel gpus
RS_Ggs: you're my idol
twintowerpower: love the boat feel his room has
twintowerpower: kinda makes me feel like a sea captain or something
TurkTurkelton: smoke weed
TurkTurkelton: nah brah
TurkTurkelton: never too early
TurkTurkelton: except when it is
Andrewnagyy: A lot of streamers in the Programming channel are mostly game engine developers lol
Andrewnagyy: I feel like the top 5 - 10 channels at any given time are featuring people writing game engines
Andrewnagyy: You have Java installed?
Andrewnagyy: :D
Andrewnagyy: You're one of the last people I would think writes in Java
benjaminr42: Right click > Open and here you go ;)
RS_Ggs: What are you building
ilendemli: iirc u need a orthograhic thingy or perpective set
tomcr00s3: laggy?
ilendemli: yes
twintowerpower: not lagging for me
SteveATZ: ordering breakfast? is that really a thing? nice
twintowerpower: it is a thing for people that don't need twitch donos
DrRobotvinnik: ah it's yor gurl ArgieB8
dorkmo: mcmuffin
SteveATZ: was she your inspiration for your rap Kappa
Andrewnagyy: Get kebab
suurrend3r: nah i really don't llike that music bro
DrRobotvinnik: what about some smashed avocado on rye? ArgieB8
DrRobotvinnik: SeemsGood
desg92: get a bagel with cream cheese
alluxua: Avocado toast sounds great and healthy
SteveATZ: if you are too broke for butter just use avocado Kappa
WistfulFella: Search YouTube for "e-dubble be a king" Thank me later, the rapper died so rip
SteveATZ: you make me hungy again XD
gluecks: da fk, do i really see this legend live on stream tonight? I was just about to head to bed
alluxua: Let us hear YOUR music
DrRobotvinnik: all chess no legs
RS_Ggs: F
WistfulFella: F
SteveATZ: monkaS
Andrewnagyy: lol
suurrend3r: lmao
DrRobotvinnik: RIP camera
SteveATZ: work on a saturday DansGame
suurrend3r: coffee coffee
RS_Ggs: ew no bread?
RS_Ggs: Everythings fine
DrRobotvinnik: errday is a workday for George
alluxua: Yeah, go out for breakfast, Geohot
SteveATZ: when i hear "hey hey hey" I always have to think about the bitconnect dude meme
Nimolo00: Is this an imac pro you have there?
DrRobotvinnik: did you see that Everybody Dance Now research @tomcr00s3 ?
DrRobotvinnik: was pretty impressive
DrRobotvinnik: https://motherboard.vice.com/en_us/article/43pebw/ai-can-manipulate-video-to-make-anybody-dance
SteveATZ: maths NotLikeThis
RS_Ggs: Whats the purpose of this project? whats twitchslam?
SteveATZ: ok, let's ask what is the goal of this project xD?
SteveATZ: what was the basic idea
DrRobotvinnik: what is the purpose of you asking questions in chat ArgieB8
SteveATZ: CoolStoryBob
alluxua: SLAM: https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Simultaneous_localization_and_mapping
Dsplits: Damn finally streaming
Luki512: Hrllo :)
DrRobotvinnik: thanks, I thought this was Wrestlemania SLAM ArgieB8
SteveATZ: LUL
Luki512: *hello :) happy to finally see you live
newtomcroose: please add 480 and ... qualitys
suurrend3r: You have to use loots
Dsplits: How many mg of l-theanine?
DrRobotvinnik: it is a fascinating 'sport'
DrRobotvinnik: Deontay Wilder and co will soon turn boxing back into WWF fingers crossed SeemsGood
Dsplits: are you not watching the fight?
alluxua: Take some omega-3 fish oil
suurrend3r: logan vs ksi
Dsplits: damn got some 3D rendering going on
Dsplits: becoming a UI designer now?
gluecks: i can see advanced raytracing incoming
th3_maj0r: Is him hard losing frames?
Dsplits: Which libraries are you using for this?
SteveATZ: xD
th3_maj0r: 6 too much, 5.5?
DrRobotvinnik: sounds reasonable
desg92: just slam amazon
morphias05: Were you at DEFCON this year? If so, how was CTF?
MessageOSRS: PogChamp // hello
SteveATZ: if we donate here on twitch, jeff bezos will get even richer TheIlluminati
DrRobotvinnik: hopefully you're affiliate otherwise Twitch gets the lot ArgieB8
SteveATZ: amazon be like "nice, mind if a take 50%?"
suurrend3r: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
Dsplits: @tomcr00s3 What do you do to stay concentrated?
suurrend3r: smoking weed
keepingtrckofthisacct: i remember you. it's been awhile since you streamed!
SteveATZ: i think beeing really smart also helps LUL
MessageOSRS: Depends 🤔
suurrend3r: LUL
gluecks: let's hear ur piano skillz
suurrend3r: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
alluxua: Yeah, donot do weeds. Weeds really damage your brain neurons
suurrend3r: U like to be anonymous
Dsplits: @tomcr00s3 you should produce a song on stream
DrRobotvinnik: Geo only plays hashkeys ArgieB8
suurrend3r: We need a new rap, nah just kidding
suurrend3r: whats your typing speed ?
SteveATZ: now i want to see him do a typeracer xD
suurrend3r: less than 120wpm?
DrRobotvinnik: he may not be fastest typer but he nibble around Tmux
SteveATZ: what kind of keyboard do you use? (obviously not the standard imac one ^^)
suurrend3r: lool
SteveATZ: kk
Dsplits: his texteditor is emacs btw
suurrend3r: vim
DrRobotvinnik: they must have baked it on the drive ArgieB8
MessageOSRS: Face of Twitch
Dsplits: @suurrend3r lol ik
SteveATZ: I also want a DXRacer, but I don't have like 300€ to spend on a chair FeelsBadMan
suurrend3r: MaxLOL MaxLOL
th3_maj0r: So... what do you wanna talking about guys?
DrRobotvinnik: tmux is the terminal multiplexer bros, just so ya know ArgieB8
alluxua: How much for that chair?
suurrend3r: Nah I don't need a DXRancer brahs
th3_maj0r: 150$-200$
alluxua: thanks!
flappieh: hey
SteveATZ: they start at like 200
Dsplits: damn the driver has to get comma.ai driving system
suurrend3r: LUL LUL LUL LUL
SteveATZ: LUL
DrRobotvinnik: ArgieB8
suurrend3r: lmao
suurrend3r: google maps
DrRobotvinnik: is the driver in a Tesla?
DrRobotvinnik: Kappa
suurrend3r: hahahhahah
SteveATZ: just let your car drive there on its own ^^ roll down a window so they can put the food in and it comes back LUL
DrRobotvinnik: dunno, if you're stuck in a hole Tesla will come get you out ArgieB8
Winnepooh_: are you saying that teslas aren't available to the average silicon valley resident?
stepaheadgold: food
alluxua: What you got for breakfast?
flappieh: what keyboard do you have? @tomcr00s3
desg92: the bart is insane there
SteveATZ: we don't talk about keyboards here Kappa
Dsplits: what's the average rent in san francisco?
Winnepooh_: so what you're saying, Fresno > SF?
SupaStylin: @Dsplits 1 kidney every 6 months
SteveATZ: how much?
Winnepooh_: 2700-3500/mo SF
SupaStylin: :kappa:
desg92: just get a hhkb
Winnepooh_: haha
RS_Ggs: What's banned from this stream? Keyboard? Emacs?
hubabuba1243: arent u a millionaire yet?
Dsplits: @tomcr00s3 Would you use emacs for 1 hour if I donate?
SteveATZ: how to donate xD? via bits?
hubabuba1243: :)
SteveATZ: food is love, food is live
th3_maj0r: Sellout
alluxua: CupFooty
SteveATZ: !paypal
suurrend3r: Ctrl Z
Dsplits: ctrl x crtl c
SteveATZ: restart
suurrend3r: F10-Q
desg92: ::quit
desg92: lmao
Dsplits: ctr x c
DrRobotvinnik: Viceland headline: veteran hacker stuck in emacs ArgieB8
dorkmo: alt f4
desg92: 656 pages?
SteveATZ: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
th3_maj0r: 20 tabs with chrome, he must have at least 128GB of ram
suurrend3r: NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis
suurrend3r: LUL LUL
th3_maj0r: nano > all
SupaStylin: @th3_maj0r (y)
SteveATZ: nice serial number LUL
SupaStylin: nano r0x
Dsplits: Damn that processor Tho
SteveATZ: needed one for a hackintosh Kappa
th3_maj0r: ahahah
Dsplits: I stay away from apple products
Dsplits: it also has a backdoor
imsooinhuman: hey i once watched one of his livestreams and he had rap battles from youtube running. does anyone have a link to them?
suurrend3r: 2 cores
Winnepooh_: that was posted in 2016
SteveATZ: do those newer CPUs still have Meltdown and Spectre?
Dsplits: you still have tesla stocks?
SteveATZ: amazon is also crazy
SteveATZ: bezos is a rich rich boi
th3_maj0r: Facebook lost a lot i think
Dsplits: He is not taking the company private
alluxua: In the past 3 years, nvidia has annual return over 100% millions ( rolling 365 days pct-change)
alluxua: * over 100%
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 bro . i am always crazy
suurrend3r: comma.ai stock prices
alluxua: Geohot, use deep learning to train stocks . It is really profitable
Winnepooh_: has comma looked into AMD GPUs in their machines, or is everyone on the Nvidia train?
newtomcroose: u shoule be rich
twintowerpower: What would train the stocks to do alluxua?
twintowerpower: you
Dsplits: yo @tomcr00s3 just heard "i want to be in love when the endgame plays out"
Dsplits: that shit is fire
SteveATZ: cheer1 how about that keyboard Kappa
alluxua: Traditional investment banks donot know how to code LSTM
linlam123: wait why do u say that reinforcement learning is a scam?
newtomcroose: block by block
Dsplits: @tomcr00s3 What is the number? for you to retired?
alluxua: When you get rich, you can get 10 pretty women standing behind you while you twitch
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 please dont come back after me , thats not gonna work now
SteveATZ: win win
suurrend3r: U need money to buy a land
JoneKone: Finland
linlam123: finland doesnt exist lol
linlam123: :D
linlam123: no land there
th3_maj0r: Zlatan bought an island
SteveATZ: some little island and chill
Dsplits: lol that shape
JoneKone: :P
Dsplits: are cybersecurity companies a scam?
newtomcroose: @tom
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 do u like liveing alone or living with your parents ?
SteveATZ: one bomb long LUL
newtomcroose: iran ?
SteveATZ: i wanna have a wakanda 2.0 LUL
Dsplits: @tomcr00s3 Are you into luxury cars?
SteveATZ: never seen black pantha?
SteveATZ: it's in the marvel universe
linlam123: do u watch any tv shows?
DrRobotvinnik: buy Mar-a-Largo, should be up for sale soon ArgieB8
SteveATZ: this movies was great
SteveATZ: cash cow
JoneKone: I agree StarTrek 3 was :( bad
Dsplits: Marvel movies are all the same but with a diff character
SteveATZ: tbh I like the marvel movies, they have nice visuals.
Dsplits: have you been to Miami?
MessageOSRS: What would be the best way to detect each of these different objects in python? https://gyazo.com/8206b01154a1d2052d7c84f0c302a6aa
MessageOSRS: Then give me a donate button 4Head
Dsplits: How are you the ladies down in Miami?
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 bro . living alone or with family ? i mean , in the house
SteveATZ: what's your paypal me link?
MessageOSRS: ^
Dsplits: @tomcr00s3 I'll donate $100 if you use emacs for an hour
JoneKone: @MessageOSRS You have to buy Eon
MessageOSRS: jaseS fuck @JoneKone
newtomcroose: who like living in tehran ?
th3_maj0r: Lol man u are easy to buy wtf
th3_maj0r: ahah
SteveATZ: when I google your paypal all I can find are the old articles that sony can use your paypal or so xD
alluxua: CupFooty CupFooty CupFooty
newtomcroose: u should search about this
SupaStylin: oh cmon
SupaStylin: my internet connection is a "#&"& crap
SupaStylin: always buffering and stuff
flappieh: subscribe and he will use emacs
newtomcroose: i wanna buy a pizza . i cant donate u bro . what should i do ?
DrRobotvinnik: put your bits where your mouth is he's accepted the challenge ArgieB8
flappieh: donating to @tomcr00s3 > eating pizza
Dsplits: sec got to ask my mommy for her creditcard
flappieh: LUL
BornHanYolo: With the video data that you saved, is the mp4 data holding data of the GPS, magnometer, and accelerimeters?
newtomcroose: who like "north of iran nature" ?
BornHanYolo: no slam
newtomcroose: i got u
quillford: is it true that block chain powered V2V is necessary for L4?
SteveATZ: TheIlluminati TheIlluminati TheIlluminati
JoneKone: What? Truth? What do you want to know about North Koreans?
newtomcroose: i love trump . because his hair is cool . and wife :)
newtomcroose: war is the 2018 ? this is a jock man
SteveATZ: Jebaited
DrRobotvinnik: ArgieB8
alluxua: Yeah, you went to china and danced on a square with middle aged women
SteveATZ: deus vult
newtomcroose: do u like physical war or computers war ? :|
SteveATZ: good old crusade
DrRobotvinnik: yeh sword fights, that's a proper war
DrRobotvinnik: that and WWF
DrRobotvinnik: ArgieB8
DrRobotvinnik: what about catapults?
SteveATZ: for HONOR SMOrc
newtomcroose: what is your comment about DARPA ?
laravells: @tomcr00s3 What are you doing for hairloss?
DrRobotvinnik: unreliable catapults, seems fair SeemsGood
th3_maj0r: Speaking of serious things, in my opinion the chair you had in the video "Hacking Lessons From geohot" looks much more comfortable than the one you have now
MessageOSRS: God damnit trying to buy bits but it's not going through
MessageOSRS: Never mind, only took about 10 minutes
laravells: @MessageOSRS omg osrs
johanuhrskov: Watch KSI vs Logan paul ;)
laravells: @johanuhrskov Hook me up with alink
Dsplits: Won't let me buy that many bits
Dsplits: send me your paypal link
desg92: !donate
Dsplits: !donate
Dsplits: No bot
newtomcroose: live alone or with family ?
Dsplits: Under his parents basement
newtomcroose: this is shit dude
Dsplits: what is?
newtomcroose: question is realy simple
newtomcroose: bro . i am 18 . give me a advice . i love computers stuffs . and weed , and space , and shity things . and "MONEY" . yeeeeeeeee
MessageOSRS: cheer250 Blame Twitch for it taking 10 years but here it is: https://gyazo.com/8206b01154a1d2052d7c84f0c302a6aa I've tried template matching, color matching and deep learning but none seem to accurately classify all individual objects 100% of the time. What approach would you take?
MessageOSRS: They are
MessageOSRS: Because the background differs every time
Tal_X_Tal: PogChamp
MessageOSRS: 🤔
newtomcroose: FrankerZ
MessageOSRS: So just slide over every sprite in the image?
MessageOSRS: And then template match each sprite
MessageOSRS: Cool thanks :)
quillford: cheer1 cheer1 cheer1 cheer1
MessageOSRS: Best $2.50 I spent this week
newtomcroose: im sad and i know it
newtomcroose: xxxtention
n1tr073: programming what
n1tr073: great
n1tr073: hi geo how r
n1tr073: ah ok i see u r working on an event driven program
suurrend3r: I learn to live with the loss
n1tr073: but can u tell me what is the input that the program response to
suurrend3r: I'll drink 100 cups of coffee
DrRobotvinnik: '50 cups of coffee and you know it's on'
Luki512: are you using the default von or any extensions?
Luki512: *vim
valgrind: emacs forsenOMEGA
linlam123: there is no donate button tho?
linlam123: or am i blind
th3_maj0r: Good people don't need a good chair
DrRobotvinnik: broski went quiet after that ArgieB8
alluxua: Guys , be nice to GeoHot. It has been a long time since the last twitch.
suurrend3r: bro, he says he got 100$ on donations
suurrend3r: nah just kidding
suurrend3r: im improving my english talking to geohot. Elon Musk is watching the stream secretly
SupaStylin: yes, i am here
SupaStylin: ^^
SupaStylin: not secretly,tho
suurrend3r: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
suurrend3r: Bro programming is life
suurrend3r: Geohot inspired me to make a typing-test in php
suurrend3r: LUL LUL
suurrend3r: with js and mysql
dorkmo: Bro-ken
dorkmo: very nice
DrRobotvinnik: TaiKwonBro
DirectorHomeless: Been a while
DirectorHomeless: Buy more ram ;)
DrRobotvinnik: ArgieB8 /
dorkmo: gnite
TheCremaxx: yo :D whats up
TheCremaxx: how did you keyboard not get broken by typing that fast :D
mattikaldi: is life meaningless?
RS_Ggs: back from your nap?
suurrend3r: I learn so much about python watching you code bro
mattikaldi: lol
mattikaldi: this some banger music
mattikaldi: trumptrumptrump
mattikaldi: fuck kinda algorithm is this
MetaExplode: go is a world with many uses
MetaExplode: :|
suurrend3r: true
MetaExplode: right to ur face
MetaExplode: :))
mattikaldi: seemsgood1
MetaExplode: :D :D
theGeekPirate: Could probably uBlock pick it
MetaExplode: just calm down
MetaExplode: and dont search go any more
alluxua: the world is full of shit
theGeekPirate: What happened is that people are used to it. We're not in Kansas (1995) anymore, Dorothy.
mattikaldi: search go and you get "why Ben Affleck went back to rehab" lol
MetaExplode: actually ur reasult of go is wway better than mine
MetaExplode: go to settings and change google settings
RS_Ggs: New default search engine
alluxua: Haha, I got to search go on my computer
THATTACHYON: which monitor to you have ?
MetaExplode: what r u test and optimizing anyway?
lsx_daniel: Hi
lsx_daniel: what are we making
lsx_daniel: i meant you
lsx_daniel: lol
alluxua: Geohot, your google go results are way better than mine. You should feel blessed
MetaExplode: no one knows @lsx_daniel
linlam123: man why do u delete ur old streams?
mattikaldi: they've been messing with your algorithm
lsx_daniel: any recommendations on where to being programming, i tuned trucks but i wanna get more into programming
linlam123: i think some ppl r just pure evil
linlam123: idk
alluxua: How you view the world, geohot?
mattikaldi: sad thing is that most people are only driven by money
RS_Ggs: get him boys
linlam123: :)
lsx_daniel: I just wanna make money so i can rebuild my 454 big block
lsx_daniel: i think making money is good but too much of it can change you in my perspective
mattikaldi: well, i agree that capitalism is where it's at though
flashingwolf122: What is being coded ?
temanning: @flashingwolf122 SLAM
mattikaldi: i live in norway and it fucking sucks tbh
temanning: Does anyone really want Communism?
alluxua: well, in this whole world, US and Canada are more and more like communism system
temanning: I think the demand is more for a socialist system
mattikaldi: lol
alluxua: Agree. Socialist system
temanning: @mattikaldi What sucks about Norway?
alluxua: people there are starving and kind of like refugees
mattikaldi: 48% tax plus a shit ton of fee's
lsx_daniel: im lost
lsx_daniel: lol
alluxua: i don't love google that much but can understand its decision. I run a lot of prediction models on google. Before sundar became the CEO, it is performance was pretty bad for about 2 years for investors
linlam123: have u read fountainhead?
mattikaldi: i'm embarrased to be Norwegian TBH
temanning: @mattikaldi Do you think the Free Healthcare is worth it?
mnero: havent heard of this in Finland :o
kuhrect: hey this isnt flare on!? :p
alluxua: Relax, geohot. it is saturday
Im_Andri: heyo
Im_Andri: what are we doing here ?
temanning: @tomcr00s3 I just saw the HD Maps Comma is releasing. Are you looking to make better version of Google Maps?
temanning: Is that not allowed?
temanning: Alright thats fair
alluxua: As far as I remember: no comma ai, no crypto, no keyboard
RS_Ggs: cant see face cam in the way
alluxua: yeah, it is pretty impressive. You are always a genius!
olack412: Why are you doing this?
olack412: Kick some bars
Tigerman143: are you still trying to recreate the driving video?
olack412: How do you stay focused for so long ?
alluxua: @olack412 , I guess that is how he grew up. He get used to this life style. I was curious this in the past as well
olack412: Is that orb slam 2?
RS_Ggs: your matrix is prob fucked
olack412: Geo on edge today somebody get the man a fucking cinnamon roll!
Winnepooh_: cinnebon
olack412: back later?
alluxua: Thanks for twitching, geohot! Go to have some fun this beautiful Saturday!
olack412: what your email ?
olack412: I need a verse
alluxua: Probably a girl?
olack412: Filter out that shit bro
olack412: Crazy & weird shit sells
olack412: Are you a cryogenics participant lol
alluxua: I want to live up to 125 years old
olack412: Lol in our lifetime thats the only way to stick around
alluxua: No, no, we hear you. We are not computers
olack412: Lmao we getting into deep thought
olack412: Has anyone used group FaceTime yet? How well does it work?
olack412: brb
alluxua: Enjoy the waffle! I appreciate you spent time with us . Your sharing always motivates me! Thank you, forgot!
alluxua: I mean: thank you, Geohot
olack412: Agreed @alluxua , but also should do this more often. We need to give that human longevity concept a deep dive.
lpdon2: *matrices